<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">MAD Practicals</string>

    <string name="string1">String 1</string>
    <string name="string2">String 2</string>


    <string name="user_name">Hridhil Thakkar</string>

    <string name="Hamlet_desc">The protagonist of the tragedy, Hamlet is a beloved prince and a thoughtful, melancholy young man. Distraught by his father\'s death, Hamlet is only made more depressed by his uncle Claudius succession to the throne and his subsequent marriage to his mother. When the ghost of the king, Hamlet\'s father, tells him that he was murdered by his brother Claudius and that Hamlet must avenge him, Hamlet becomes almost suicidal and obsessed with revenge. He is slowly driven mad by his inability to act on this instruction.

        Very intelligent, Hamlet decides to fake madness in order to fool his uncle and those loyal to him while he uncovers whether Claudius is guilty for his father\'s death—although often his mental health is genuinely in question. Worried about his own guilt, Hamlet also becomes hateful, despising his uncle, voicing anger at his mother, frustrated with his traitorous friends, and alienating Ophelia (whom he once courted). His anger borders on ruthlessness, and he is responsible for numerous deaths throughout the play, but he never loses his reflective and melancholy traits.</string>

    <string name="killing_hemm">Teddy Alexander is about to have a bad day that changes his life forever. He\'s found his teacher\'s bad side, and she wants him expelled. Although learning is his favorite thing to do, and Teddy is good at it, what he really wants is a friend. Friendship can be hard to find and sometimes fades, but Teddy keeps trying.

        Even at a young age, Teddy is kind, with a strong sense of right and wrong. When Mrs. Braunshausen gives away his turn to feed Mr. Chompers, the class tortoise, Teddy is not happy about it. He loves Mr. Chompers.

        This is the story of a young genius who grows into a hopeless romantic. We follow his life from age six, through high school at age twelve, and on to his decision to go back to college (for a PhD in Literature) after finishing his bachelor\'s and master\'s degrees in physics at eighteen.

        A coming of age novel about life, decisions, love, and genius.

        Killing Hemingway is a perfect book for teen and young adult readers, those who never liked Hemingway, and anyone who enjoys a bit of humorous fiction with a side of cute.</string>

    <string name="ThieteenReasonsWhy">You can’t stop the future.
        You can’t rewind the past.
        The only way to learn the secret . . . is to press play.

        Clay Jensen returns home from school to find a strange package with his name on it lying on his porch. Inside he discovers several cassette tapes recorded by Hannah Baker–his classmate and crush–who committed suicide two weeks earlier. Hannah\'s voice tells him that there are thirteen reasons why she decided to end her life. Clay is one of them. If he listens, he\'ll find out why.

        Clay spends the night crisscrossing his town with Hannah as his guide. He becomes a firsthand witness to Hannah\'s pain, and as he follows Hannah\'s recorded words throughout his town, what he discovers changes his life forever.</string>

    <string name="terminal_rage">In this critically acclaimed and bestselling international thriller, FBI hostage-negotiator Alexander Blackwell is dragged out of a dishonorable retirement to negotiate with a terrorist leader who has taken hostages in a Manhattan skyscraper. In a world where the truth has become B-roll, exposing the true identity of his enigmatic adversary is the only thing Blackwell can do to prevent death and destruction of unprecedented proportions. But how do you unravel the identity of a man who does not exist? A frenetic pace, a hair-raising plot that hops around the globe, hard-hitting character beats, crisp prose, dexterous timing, the mother of all twists, and hands down one of the most interesting villains this side of Keyser Söze from The Usual Suspects make Terminal Rage a modern-day cult classic that defiantly redefines its genre.</string>

    <string name="philosophers_stone">Ten-year-old Harry Potter is an orphan who lives in the fictional London suburb of Little Whinging, Surrey, with the Dursleys: his uncaring Aunt Petunia, loathsome Uncle Vernon, and spoiled cousin Dudley. The Dursleys barely tolerate Harry, and Dudley bullies him. One day Harry is astonished to receive a letter addressed to him in the cupboard under the stairs (where he sleeps). Before he can open the letter, however, Uncle Vernon takes it. Letters for Harry subsequently arrive each day, in increasing numbers, but Uncle Vernon tears them all up, and finally, in an attempt to escape the missives, the Dursleys go to a miserable shack on a small island. On Harry\'s 11th birthday, a giant named Hagrid arrives and reveals that Harry is a wizard and that he has been accepted at the Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. He also sheds light on Harry\'s past, informing the boy that his parents, a wizard and a witch, were killed by the evil wizard Voldemort and that Harry acquired the lightning-bolt scar on his forehead during the fatal confrontation.

        Upon arrival at the school, the students are sorted into one of four houses—Gryffindor, Hufflepuff, Ravenclaw, or Slytherin. Harry ends up in Gryffindor, and during his eventful first year at Hogwarts he becomes close friends with two other members of the house, Ron Weasley, who comes from an old wizarding family, and Hermione Granger, whose parents are Muggles (those who are not magical). Harry also finds that he has an enemy in Draco Malfoy (Slytherin). In addition, Harry\'s prowess in flying on a broomstick makes him a star of Gryffindor\'s Quidditch team. Hoping to get Harry and his friends into trouble, Draco tricks them into leaving their rooms one night, a violation of school rules. While trying to avoid being caught, they discover a three-headed dog guarding a trapdoor. Harry gradually comes to the conclusion that Professor Snape, who teaches Potions, dislikes him intensely and is trying to get hold of whatever is behind the trapdoor. Harry receives his father\'s cloak of invisibility as a Christmas gift, and, while exploring under the cloak\'s cover, he finds the Mirror of Erised, in which he can see his parents. Later, headmaster Albus Dumbledore explains that the mirror shows the viewer\'s deepest desire.

        Harry, Ron, and Hermione deduce that the treasure under the trapdoor is the Philosopher\'s Stone, which can transform metal into gold and can also confer immortality. They later discover that Voldemort has been killing unicorns in the Forbidden Forest and drinking their blood, another way to achieve immortality. The trio comes to believe that Snape is in league with the evil wizard. After learning that Hagrid revealed the secret way to lull the three-headed dog to sleep to a suspicious stranger, whom they believe to be either Snape or Voldemort, they are certain that the Philosopher\'s Stone is in danger. The three classmates use the cloak of invisibility on a secret mission to get the Stone themselves to keep it from Voldemort. After getting past the dog and defeating various protective spells, Harry reaches the room in which the Stone is hidden and is surprised to find the perpetually nervous Professor Quirrell there. Quirrell fails to figure out how to retrieve the Stone from the Mirror of Erised (the final protective measure) and forces Harry to try. When standing in front of the mirror, wishing only to protect the Stone and not use it for himself, Harry feels the Stone\'s weight in his pocket but refuses to tell Quirrell that he has it. Quirrell unwraps his turban, revealing Voldemort\'s face on the back of his head. Voldemort explains that he has been sharing Quirrell\'s body until he can get to the Stone and become fully alive again, and Voldemort/Quirrell and Harry fight for possession of the Stone, until Harry blacks out. He awakens in the infirmary and learns that Dumbledore saved him, the Stone is to be destroyed, and Voldemort escaped.</string>

    <string name="chamber_of_secrets">Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets begins when Harry is spending a miserable summer with his only remaining family, the Dursleys. During a dinner party hosted by his uncle and aunt, Harry is visited by Dobby, a house-elf. Dobby warns Harry not to return to Hogwarts, the magical school for wizards that Harry attended the previous year. Harry politely disregards the warning, and Dobby wreaks havoc in the kitchen, infuriating the Dursleys. The Dursleys angrily imprison Harry in his room for the rest of the summer. Luckily, Harry\'s friend Ron Weasley steals Harry away in a flying car, and Harry happily spends the rest of the summer at the Weasley home.

        While shopping for school supplies with the Weasleys, Harry has two unfortunate encounters. He first encounters Lockhart, one of his teachers, who demands to be in a photo shoot with Harry. Harry then encounters Lucius Malfoy, the evil father of one of Harry\'s enemies, who almost starts a fight with Mr. Weasley. As Harry prepares to return to Hogwarts, he finds that he and Ron are unable to enter the magically invisible train platform, so they fly the Weasley car to Hogwarts. They land messily, and both boys are given detentions. Lockhart, who believes Harry flew the car to get attention, lectures Harry.

        Quidditch practices begin and Draco Malfoy is the new Slytherin seeker. On the field, he calls Hermione a mudblood, insulting her Muggle heritage. After taunting Hermione, Draco is the suspect when, on Halloween night, someone petrifies the school caretaker\'s cat and writes a threatening message. Before the cat is attacked, Harry twice hears an eerie voice. He hears it first during his detention and second during a party, moments before the cat is attacked. Everybody in the school is alarmed. By doing some research, Harry, Ron, and Hermione learn that fifty years ago a chamber at Hogwarts was opened and a student was killed.

        Playing for Gryffindor, Harry wins the Quidditch match against Slytherin. During the game, an enchanted ball hits Harry and causes him to lose the bones in his arm. Dobby, a house elf, has enchanted the ball in an effort to have Harry injured and sent home. That night, Harry sees the body of a first-year who has been petrified arrive at the hospital. Soon after, Lockhart begins a dueling club. During the first meeting, Harry terrifies his fellow students by speaking in Parseltongue to a snake. Harry\'s ability frightens the others because only the heir of Slytherin, who is responsible for opening the chamber, would have the ability to converse with snakes. Harry comes under further suspicion when he stumbles upon the petrified bodies of Justin Finch-Fletchley and Nearly-Headless Nick.

        Determined to catch the culprit, Ron, Harry and Hermione brew a potion called Polyjuice. The potion allows them to assume the bodies of Slytherins and question Malfoy on the Chamber of Secrets. They find out that Malfoy is not the heir of Slytherin. No more attacks occur for a while, and right before Valentine\'s Day, Harry finds a diary in the broken toilet. The diary belongs to a ghost named Moaning Myrtle who haunts the girls restroom. Harry writes in the diary, which responds by writing back. Through this dialogue, Harry meets Tom Riddle, a boy who many years before had accused Hagrid of opening the Chamber of Secrets.

        Hermione and a Ravenclaw girl are mysteriously petrified. Harry and Ron venture out of the castle to question Hagrid. Before they reach Hagrid, the Minister of Magic, Cornelius Fudge, and Lucius Malfoy remove Dumbledore and Hagrid from Hogwarts. As Hagrid is led away, he instructs the boys that by following the spiders, they can find out about the Chamber monster. Several nights later, Harry and Ron sneak into the Forbidden Forest to follow the spiders. They discover the monster who killed the girl fifty years before was not a spider, that the girl\'s body was found in a bathroom, and that Hagrid is innocent. The boys are almost killed by a colony of giant spiders. As they escape, Harry and Ron decide that Moaning Myrtle must have been the girl killed by the monster.

        A few days later, Ron and Harry discover a piece of paper with a description of a basilisk on it in Hermion\'s frozen hand. They deduce the Chamber monster is a basilisk. Before the boys can act on their knowledge, the teachers announce that Ginny Weasley has been taken into the chamber. Ron, Harry, and Lockhart slide down a secret passage in Myrtle\'s bathroom to underground tunnels. When Lockhart accidentally curses himself, Ron helps him and Harry leaves them behind. Harry enters the Chamber of Secrets and encounters Ginny\'s still body and Tom Riddle. Tom turns out to be a younger version of Voldemort, who has been enchanting Ginny through his journal. Harry calls for help from Dumbledore. A phoenix and a magic hat arrive. Tom summons a basilisk, but the phoenix punctures its eyes. The hat produces a sword, which Harry uses to kill the giant snake. Harry sticks a basilisk fang through the diary, destroying Tom. Ginny wakes up.

        Harry explains his adventure to Dumbledore. Lucius Malfoy storms into the office with his house-elf, Dobby, and Harry frees Dobby from by tricking Lucius into giving Dobby a sock. All is well in the castle as the students leave for their summer vacations.</string>

    <string name="prisoner_of_azkaban">Harry is back with the Dursleys, where he sees on the Muggle news that a prisoner named Sirius Black has escaped. During Vernon\'s sister Marge\'s visit to Privet Drive, Harry accidentally inflates her after she makes rude comments about his parents. This forces him to pack his bags and leave the house. Just as he\'s realizing he has no way to connect with anyone in the wizarding world, he\'s picked up by the Knight Bus, an emergency travel service for stranded witches and wizards. He travels to Diagon Alley where he meets Cornelius Fudge, the Minister of Magic. Fudge tells Harry that he has to stay in Diagon Alley for the remaining three weeks before school starts again.

        The night before the Hogwarts Express departs, Harry learns that Sirius Black is a convicted murderer, who is believed to want to murder Harry. The next day, a Dementor boards the Hogwarts Express, causing Harry to faint. Luckily, the new Defence Against the Dark Arts teacher Remus Lupin is there to fend it off. Harry, Ron, and Hermione learn that the Dementors will be patrolling around the school in order to protect Harry from Sirius.

        Harry has several problems with the Dementors, including an event where during a quidditch match, he faints and falls off his broomstick 50 feet in the air. His broom is smashed by the Whomping Willow. Lupin, outside of class, teaches Harry to repel Dementors using the Patronus Charm.

        Without a permission slip signed by a guardian, Harry is unable to participate in weekend excursions to Hogsmeade with the rest of the upperclassmen. George and Fred Weasley give Harry a Marauder\'s Map, which details hidden passages in Hogwarts and live markers of the people who travel them. Harry uses the map to sneak to Hogsmeade where he overhears a conversation among faculty members about how Sirius Black was a family friend and godfather to Harry, who betrayed his parents and provided Voldemort with the location of their safehouse. Black was also convicted for killing thirteen Muggles and their friend Peter Pettigrew.

        Ron and Hermione\'s friendship suffers because Ron believes that Hermione\'s cat, Crookshanks, ate his rat, Scabbers. At Christmas, Harry receives a state-of-the-art Firebolt broom as a gift, but there is no card or indication of who sent it. Fearing that it might be cursed, Hermione reports it to McGonagall.

        Harry, Ron, and Hermione try to save Hagrid\'s hippogriff Buckbeak from execution after it attacks Draco Malfoy. Their efforts are unsuccessful, but Scabbers reappears shortly after Buckbeak is executed.

        Ron chases Scabbers, only to be attacked by a big black dog who drags him through a tunnel under the Whomping Willow into the Shrieking Shack. Harry and Hermione follow him to find Ron and Sirius, who is an Animagus and is able to transform into a dog at will. Lupin enters and explains that he is a werewolf, which led his friends James Potter, Peter Pettigrew, and Sirius Black to become Animagi. Lupin tells them that Scabbers is Pettigrew in his animal form, who is hiding from Sirius after he framed him for murdering Harry\'s parents and thirteen Muggles.

        Severus Snape arrives to apprehend Sirius, but Harry knocks him out. Lupin and Sirius transform Peter into his human form and prepare to kill him. Harry stops them, telling him that his father would have not wanted it.

        At night, Lupin turns into a werewolf and becomes violent. Peter escapes again, but Sirius prevents Lupin from attacking the others. Dementors approach them and the three lose consciousness. When they wake up in the hospital, Harry, Ron, and Hermione learn that Sirius has been sentenced to receive the Dementor\'s Kiss, which removes the soul of the recipient. Dumbledore advises Hermione to use her time-turner, to go back in time and save Buckbeak, who later carries Sirius away to safety.</string>

    <string name="goblet_of_fire">The fourth book begins with Harry seeing Lord Voldemort kill Frank Bryce in a vision, and waking up in pain from the scar on his forehead. Harry and Hermione then join the Weasley family at the Quidditch World Cup, where Harry meets Cedric Diggory, who is there with his father. Following the match, followers of Voldemort attack the site and for the first time in thirteen years the Dark Mark is fired into the sky, causing more panic. Winky the elf, of the Barty Crouch Senior House, is accused of the deed when she is seen with Harry\'s wand, which is said to have released the Mark. Harry had lost the wand during the attack. Hermione then forms a society to protect the house elves.

        Meanwhile, at Hogwarts, Dumbledore introduces Alastor Moody as the teacher of Defense Against the Dark Arts for the year, and announces that the Triwizard Tournament will be hosted by Hogwarts. Only those aged seventeen or older are permitted to enter the tournament. Students from other wizarding academies including Beauxbatons and Durmstrang will stay at Hogwarts for the year to participate in the event, which is being held for the first time in 202 years. When Halloween arrives the Goblet of Fire selects Fleur Delacour of Beauxbatons, Viktor Krum from Durmstrang, and Cedric Diggory of Hogwarts as competitors in the tournament. It then gives Harry\'s name as well, which leads to suspicion and anger from many, but also forces Harry to compete. Ron especially becomes jealous as Harry becomes the center of attention, and will not speak to him.

        Harry learns from Hagrid that the first event in the contest involves dragons. Harry needs to pass a Hungarian Horntail in order to reach a golden egg containing a hint that will help him in the next task. With the use of his Firebolt broomstick, Harry finishes the task and ties with Krum for first place. As time has passed, Harry and Ron have gotten over their differences. Ron has come to see the danger involved with the tournament. Harry opens the egg and all it does is shriek. Hermione takes Harry and Ron to the kitchen, where the elves are working. They meet Winky there, along with Dobby, an old friend of Harry\'s. Dobby is the only one of the elves who appreciates the freedom that he has. During this time period a reporter named Rita Skeeter publishes gossip-filled articles in The Daily Prophet containing many lies about the events and the people at Hogwarts. Hermione, Harry, and Hagrid are among her targets.

        As the annual Yule Ball grows near, Harry needs to invite someone and asks Cho Chang, on whom he has a crush. She, however, has already agreed to go with Cedric. Harry and Ron then ask Parvati and Padma Patil. When Hermione arrives with Krum, Ron becomes jealous. Cedric tries to help Harry with the egg and tells him to bring it to the prefects bathroom. Harry does not listen, as he is preoccupied with his jealousy over Cho. When Harry finally heeds Cedric\'s advice he takes the egg into the bathroom and Moaning Myrtle, a ghost, tells him that he needs to listen to it underwater. He is then able to decipher the words, which tell him that his next task is to recover something he will miss. He looks for spells that will help him at the Black Lake, where he will need to continue the task. After rescuing Ron from under the lake and then Fleur\'s sister Gabrielle as well, Harry and Cedric end up tied for the lead.

        Several weeks prior to the final task, Harry and Krum meet Crouch, who seems insane but is able to ask Harry to get Dumbledore. Harry does so and when he gets back with Dumbledore, Crouch is gone. Harry continues to get ready for the last task, which is a hedge maze. In the maze, Harry has to overcome Krum, who is under a spell, and to save Cedric. Together Harry and Cedric reach the cup and touch it. They find themselves transported to a graveyard where Cedric is killed by Peter Pettigrew, who also uses Harry\'s blood to resurrect Lord Vlodemort. Voldemort calls for his Death Eaters and ultimately challenges Harry to a duel. When their wands make contact, Voldemort\'s releases all of the recent spells it has cast and visions appear of his victims, including Harry\'s parents, who distract Voldemort, allowing Harry to escape to Hogwarts with Cedric\'s body.

        Back at Hogwarts, Harry learns that Moody is Voldmort\'s servant and is the one who put Harry\'s name into the Goblet of Fire. Before Moody is able to kill Harry, Dumbledore arrives with McGonagall and Snape. As events unravel, Harry becomes the winner of the Triwizard Tournament. With the tournament ended, Voldemort having returned, Harry looking for romance, and tensions growing between Ron and Hermione, the ending of Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire ties up loose ends while at the same time paving the way for the fifth book in the series, Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.</string>

    <string name="order_of_phoenix">The story opens over summer vacation. Harry Potter has spent the whole summer at his Aunt Petunia\'s house listening to the news, seeking signs of an attack. One evening, taunting his cousin Dudley with the threat of using magic on him, they are attacked by Dementors. Harry uses magic to fight them off, landing Harry in deep trouble with the Ministry of Magic; he is threatened with expulsion from Hogwarts. At a hearing at the Ministry of Magic, however, Harry is allowed to remain in school.

        Harry is met by a group of wizards led by Mad-Eye Moody, Professor Lupin, Nymphadora Tonks, and Kingsley Shacklebolt and taken to Sirius Black\'s childhood home. Harry\'s friends Hermione Granger and Ron Weasley are there. They explain to Harry that the house is the headquarters of the Order of the Phoenix, a secret organization of wizards dedicated to battling Voldemort and his Death Eaters. The Order has learned that Voldemort is seeking an object, possibly a weapon. Fearing the panic the knowledge would cause, the Ministry of Magic, led by Cornelius Fudge, refuses to admit that Voldemort has returned, and thus are doing nothing to combat him.

        At school, Harry meets the new Defense Against the Dark Arts professor, Dolores Umbridge. The Daily Prophet newspaper is still printing lies about him, but Harry decides to keep his head down and concentrate on his studies. Umbridge refuses to teach any actual defense spells, claiming they are unnecessary, and she and Harry clash. When Umbridge is named High Inquisitor, giving her the authority to evaluate all faculty members and allowing her to monitor all communication in and out of the school, Harry, Hermione, and Ron form their own Defense Against the Dark Arts group, calling themselves Dumbledore\'s Army after the school\'s headmaster, Albus Dumbledore. Dozens of other students join them to train in defensive spells.

        Harry has a recurring dream that he is walking down a hallway in the Ministry of Magic and enters a room filled with glass spheres. He also has a dream where he is a snake attacking Ron\'s father. When he wakes up, he is taken to Dumbledore. Members of the Order of the Phoenix race to Mr. Weasley, rescuing him. Harry is told that Voldemort has been invading his mind; Dumbledore orders Occlumency lessons so Harry can learn to resist these attacks. Harry has difficulty with this new training, however, and his lightning-bolt scar pulses painfully every time Voldemort feels extreme emotion.

        Umbridge discovers Dumbledore\'s Army. Dumbledore takes responsibility in order to save the children from expulsion, leaving the castle. Umbridge is named headmistress. As the students are finishing up their O.W.L. examinations, Harry has another dream. This time, he sees his godfather, Sirius Black, being tortured. Hermione is concerned that Voldemort is using these dreams to lure Harry into a trap, but Harry is determined to save Sirius. Harry sneaks into Umbridge\'s office to use her fireplace to communicate with those in Sirius Black\'s house. Creature the house elf tells him that Sirius is at the Ministry of Magic. Harry and his friends are caught by Umbridge. They trick her, telling her they are hiding a weapon in the forest for Dumbledore. She accompanies them into the forest where they are stopped by centaurs. Umbridge insults the centaurs with racial slurs. Outraged, they carry her off. Harry, Hermione, Ron and their friends Ginny Weasley (Ron\'s sister), Luna Lovegood, and Neville Longbottom mount thestrals and fly to the Ministry of Magic.

        At the Ministry, Sirius is nowhere to be found. Harry locates the room he has been dreaming of and finds that one of the glass spheres has his name and Voldemort\'s on it. The Death Eaters attack. Harry and his friends have some initial success defending themselves, surprising the Death Eaters with their skills, but begin to lose ground until members of the Order of the Phoenix arrive, turning the tide. During the battle, Harry passes this sphere to Neville, whose pocket rips, causing the glass sphere to shatter. Sirius Black is killed by his cousin Bellatrix Lestrange. Dumbledore arrives, rounding up and binding the Death Eaters.

        Harry chases after Bellatrix. Voldemort arrives. As he is attacking Harry, Dumbledore comes to Harry\'s rescue, dueling with Voldemort. Voldemort and Bellatrix escape. Back at Hogwarts, Dumbledore explains to Harry that the sphere was a prophecy telling of a power Harry possesses unknown to Voldemort: Love. The prophecy states that Harry will either kill Voldemort or be killed by him—“neither can live while the other survives.” Dumbledore explains that this is why Harry must spend his summers with his Aunt Petunia—his mother\'s love protects him, and he must maintain the blood link to that love by living in his aunt\'s house. Knowing the summer will be miserable, Harry accepts his fate and returns to his aunt\'s house where he will spend another summer listening to the news and waiting for something terrible to happen.</string>

    <string name="half_blood_prince">Severus Snape, a teacher at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry and a member of the Order of the Phoenix, meets with Narcissa Malfoy, Draco\'s mother, and Bellatrix Lestrange. Narcissa worries about her son\'s life being at risk. He has been given a dangerous mission by Lord Voldemort. Bellatrix accuses Snape of being disloyal, but he proves himself in her eyes by making an Unbreakable Vow with Narcissa, swearing on his own life that he will protect Draco in his mission.

        Meanwhile, Dumbledore has picked up Harry from his aunt and uncle\'s house with the intention of bringing him to the Burrow, the Weasleys home. They make a quick stop at Horace Slughorn\'s house. Dumbledore uses Harry to convince Slughorn, an old potions teacher at Hogwarts, to return to teach. The two then go to the Burrow to meet Hermione and Ron. The three kids receive their Ordinary Wizarding Level (O.W.L.) results. They go to Diagon Alley to pick up their school supplies. Harry, Ron, and Hermione follow their nemesis, Draco Malfoy, into Borgin and Burkes, a dark arts supplier. Harry is suspicious of Draco right away, believing him to be a Death Eater.

        On returning to Hogwarts, Dumbledore announces that Slughorn has returned to teach potions, while Snape, the previous potions teacher, will be taking on the role of defense against the dark arts teacher. Harry gets a textbook that used to belong to someone named “The Half-Blood Prince,” a secret student from the past who writes tips throughout the book. Because of this, Harry excels at potions. The Slughorn holds a competition in class; Harry wins the prize—a bottle of “Liquid Luck.” Hermione is not pleased—she feels Harry is not earning his recognition honestly, and that the Half-Blood Prince should not be trusted.

        Dumbledore believes that in order to defeat Voldemort, Harry must learn about Voldemort\'s past. Dumbledore schedules regular meetings with Harry. He has Harry use his pensieve to observe the memories of people who have had contact with Voldemort. Harry learns about Voldemort\'s family and his life, which is obsessed with power and eternal life. One memory is of Tom Riddle (Voldemort\'s name before he changed it) as a student at Hogwarts interacting with Slughorn. The memory has been tampered with, however, and Dumbledore sets Harry the task of getting the true memory from Slughorn. This memory would confirm Dumbledore\'s suspicions about Voldemort\'s near-invincibility.

        Harry uses a bit of the Liquid Luck to get the unedited memory while at Aragog the Spider\'s funeral. In the memory, Slughorn tells Riddle about Horcruxes, the process of splitting one\'s soul and saving it to an object. Voldemort has made six of them, making him virtually immortal, along with his own body, the seventh. In order to kill him, the Horcruxes must be destroyed. Two have already been destroyed, but four others remain.

        When Ron finds out that Hermione kissed Viktor Krum in the past, he is angry. He goes out with Lavender Brown to make Hermione jealous. Ron is nearly killed in an accident, allowing Hermione and Ron to make up again. Lavender dumps Ron when she sees Ron and Hermione together. Harry\'s feelings for Ginny grow, but he is nervous about pursuing them because of his friendship with Ron. An exciting win for the Quidditch team results in a victorious celebration, and Harry and Ginny finally begin their relationship.

        Near the end of the year, Harry and Dumbledore take a trip to a cave, where Dumbledore believes a Horcrux, Slytherin\'s locket, is hidden. They travel through a secret passage, cross a large black lake to a small island in the middle. The locket can only be retrieved by drinking the potion in the basin holding the locket, which Dumbledore does. Inferi, dead bodies bewitched to move on a Dark Wizard\'s behalf, attack from the depths of the lake, but Dumbledore and Harry fight them off and escape. They return to Hogwarts with the locket, where a Dark Mark hovers above a tower. They ascend the tower and are met by Draco and several other Death Eaters. Dumbledore puts the body-bind spell on Harry, who is wearing his invisibility cloak, hiding him from the Death Eaters. Draco disarms Dumbledore and threatens to kill him. This, it turns out, was his mission from Voldemort. Draco hesitates, though, and Snape arrives, killing Dumbledore. The battle is raging throughout Hogwarts, but Harry pursues Snape. Snape reveals himself to be the Half-Blood Prince and escapes with the rest of the Death Eaters.

        At Dumbledore\'s funeral, Harry breaks up with Ginny, citing the danger their relationship puts her in. The locket turns out to be a fraud, with only a note written by “R.A.B.” Harry is so frustrated and devastated that he refuses to return to school next year, instead going to search for the Horcruxes. Ron and Hermione vow to join him.</string>

    <string name="deathly_hallows">The Deathly Hallows opens just after the events of the previous novel, The Half-Blood Prince, in which Harry and his friends Hermione and Ron learned about Lord Voldemort\'s Horcruxes – vestiges of his power and soul. Returning to Hogwarts after tracking one of these down, Harry\'s longtime mentor and the headmaster of Hogwarts, Albus Dumbledore, is killed.

        To protect Harry, members of the secret organization The Order of the Phoenix transport him to a safe house – a dangerous venture that gets a member of the Order killed. There is a brief respite for Ron\'s brother Bill\'s wedding, but the wedding is attacked by Voldemort\'s Death Eaters. With Dumbledore dead, Voldemort takes over the magic world\'s government, the Ministry of Magic. Harry, Ron, and Hermione escape the attack at Bill\'s wedding, leaving to find the last four Horcruxes: three objects owned by Hogwarts co-founders Salazar Slytherin, Helga Hufflepuff, and Rowena Ravenclaw, and Nagini, Voldemort\'s snake familiar.

        Harry and his friends discover that Salazar Slytherin\'s locket was stolen by Regulus Black, the Death Eater brother of Harry\'s benevolent godfather, Sirius, and later ending up in the custody of the Dolores Umbridge at Ministry of Magic. Sneaking into the building, they find the locket. Unable to destroy it, they take turns wearing it. Eventually, the locket\'s influence is so destructive that Ron abandons his friends.

        Pressing on, Harry and Hermione try to track down anyone who might be able to help. One such person is magic historian Bathilda Bagshot who lives near the house where Harry\'s parents were killed. However, Bathilda turns out to be the shape-shifting snake Nagini in disguise—the real Bathilda is dead. After barely escaping and breaking his wand in the process, Harry and Hermione are led to camp by a lake where Harry finds the powerful sword of another Hogwarts founder, Godric Gryffindor. Just as the locket is about to kill Harry, Ron reappears, grabs the sword, and destroys the locket with it.

        Using a clue found in a book Dumbledore left them, the three friends learn about the Deathly Hallows – three mythical objects from an old magical fairy tale – Dumbledore\'s Elder Wand, which can\'t be beaten; the Resurrection Stone, able to bring back the dead; and an Invisibility Cloak. Harry realizes that Voldemort is searching for the Elder Wand when he sees a vision of Voldemort breaking into Dumbledore\'s tomb to steal the wand. Harry also figures out that the Stone is sealed in another present Dumbledore gave him, and that the cloak is the Invisibility Cloak Harry inherited from his father.

        After being captured by Voldemort followers and dueling with one of Voldemort\'s most powerful Death Eaters Bellatrix Lestrange, who takes away Gryffindor\'s sword, the trio escapes and finds another Horcrux – Helga Hufflepuff\'s golden cup in the Lestrange vault. At the same time, Voldemort realizes that they are hunting his Horcruxes, and goes about securing them. Harry has a vision that another Horcrux is at Hogwarts.

        They fight through setbacks and ambushes to get into the school, and their search for the next Horcrux leads them to Rowena Ravenclaw\'s diadem. This object is destroyed by an errant spell cast by one of Voldemort\'s minions trying to kill Harry. Many of their friends are killed in the ensuing Battle of Hogwarts.

        Voldemort is disappointed with the Elder Wand. He assumes this is because he has to kill its previous owner, whom he thinks is Professor Snape, who throughout the series had antagonized Harry and been assumed to be on Voldemort\'s side. However, a dying Snape gives Harry some of his memories, revealing to Harry that he has been on the side of good all along. Through Snape\'s memories, Harry learns that he himself is one of Voldemort\'s Horcruxes – when Voldemort didn\'t succeed in killing Harry as a baby, a piece of Voldemort\'s soul was trapped inside Harry. Knowing what he has to do, Harry goes to Voldemort\'s hideout in the Forbidden Forrest and allows Voldemort to kill him using the Killing Curse spell.

        Harry finds himself in a dreamlike place speaking to Dumbledore, who reveals that because of the mistakes Voldemort has made along the way, Harry can return to life if he chooses. Harry reawakens in the forest and plays dead. When Voldemort tries to show off Harry\'s corpse to the defenders of Hogwarts, Harry\'s friend Neville Longbottom kills Nagini, Voldemort\'s last Horcrux, meaning that Voldemort can now be killed. Harry escapes using his Invisibility Cloak.

        The final showdown takes place with many Death Eater casualties. A weakened Voldemort tries to kill Harry with the Killing Curse, but the Elder Wand refuses to recognize Voldemort as its true master and the spell rebounds on Voldemort, destroying him forever. The wizarding world can now be restored to peace.

        The novel ends with an Epilogue set nineteen years later, as an adult Harry is packing his children off to Hogwarts. The book ends with the words: The scar had not pained Harry for nineteen years. All was well.</string>

    <string name="curse_child">The book begins at King\'s Cross Station, with Harry\'s and Hermione\'s respective children—Albus Potter and Rose Granger-Weasley—going off to Hogwarts for the first time. Albus is afraid he will break the family tradition and be sorted into Slytherin rather than Gryffindor. On the Hogwarts Express, Albus makes friends with Scorpius Malfoy, the son of Draco Malfoy. Scorpius is sorted into Slytherin, then in a complete surprise Albus Potter is sorted into Slytherin. Rose is sorted into Gryffindor and becomes popular as Albus shows no particular magical aptitude, thus widening the distance between her and her cousin Albus. Scorpius and Albus are friends, but rumors about Scorpius\'s birth cause him to be an outcast.

        Draco Malfoy is tormented by rumors that Voldemort used a Time-Turner to impregnate his wife Astoria to give birth to Scorpius. He asks Harry Potter for a statement that all Time-Turners have all been destroyed. Harry is then visited by Amos Diggory and his niece Delphi, who each want Harry to go back in time to the Triwizard tournament and save his son, Cedric, since he was an innocent victim of Lord Voldemort.

        Over a holiday, Harry arrives to give Albus a present: his own baby blanket. The gesture feels empty; Albus and Harry argue about Albus\'s difficulties at school and Harry says he sometimes wishes Albus wasn\'t his son. Albus leaves to go back to Hogwarts and Harry\'s scar begins to hurt for the first time in nineteen years.

        Albus and Scorpius offer to help Amos and Delphi Diggory by using the Time-Turner to go back in time to stop Cedric\'s death by saving him from winning the Triwizard Tournament. They use Polyjuice Potion to steal a Time-Turner from the Ministry of Magic and sabotage Cedric in the first round of the Tri-wizard tournament.

        Harry and Draco discover Albus and Scorpius outside Hogwarts when they are transported back to the present, as the Time-Turner has a five-minute limit. After being warned of a dark cloud around his son by the centaur Bane, Harry tells Albus to keep away from Scorpius.

        The next day, the meddling with time yields small changes. Ron is married to Padma Patil, Hermione is a teacher at Hogwarts, and Albus is now in Gryffindor. They go back in time to sabotage Cedric\'s Second Task of the tournament. When they return to the future, Scorpius can\'t find Albus and is informed by Headmistress Umbridge that Harry Potter was killed during a failed coup on the school at the Battle of Hogwarts; Albus does not exits. Scorpius goes to Severus Snape, who in this narrative is still alive, to ask for help. Scorpius explains that Harry Potter is alive and Voldemort is dead in another world. Snape leads them to the base of the resistance, The Order of the Phoenix. They use the Time-Turner to go back to the Triwizard tournament and Albus is prevented from casting his spell on Cedric. When they return, Dementors arrive and suck out Hermione and Ron\'s souls. Snape is also killed.

        Scorpius goes back in time and finds Albus alive. Scorpius wants to destroy the Time-Turner. They hand it to Delphi but realize she is not a Diggory; she is the daughter of Lord Voldemort. Delphi wants Albus to travel in time to make Voldemort ruler by humiliating Cedric or she will kill Scorpius. She takes them back in time to the Third Task maze and tortures Scorpius, but is struck by Cedric who thinks it is part of the tournament. Delphi, Albus, and Scorpius pick up the time-turner and Delphi destroys it.

        They stop at an unknown period. Albus and Scorpius discover that they have been transported to the day that Harry\'s parents died. Delphi aims to stop Voldemort from attempting to kill Harry in the first place, so that when he kills Harry, the curse will not be rebounded.

        Albus and Scorpius send a message to Harry in the present through the baby blanket that Harry gave to Albus with the date and time they are at. Draco has indeed concealed a Time-Turner, and Harry, Ginny, Draco, Ron, and Hermione travel in time to the date: Halloween Eve, 1981. When they arrive Harry transforms into Voldemort to lure Delphi. Delphi explains to him that she is the child of an affair between Voldemort and Bellatrix Lestrange. The transfiguration begins to fade and Delphi realizes it\'s Harry, not Voldemort. They duel, and Albus helps his father to beat Delphi. They then hear the real Voldemort arriving to kill Harry\'s parents and realize they cannot intervene or risk changing the future. Harry watches his parents being murdered.

        In the present, Scorpius asks out Rose Granger-Weasley who declines, but give him hope for the future. Harry pledges to be a better father and explains that Dumbledore and Snape were great, but flawed men, and he must not feel obligated to live up to their accomplishments. Both Harry and Albus are filled with hope for their relationship.</string>

</resources>